Guide to the Friends and Residents of Greater Gowanus records 2017.011
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 4: Subject files
  - Industrial business zone 2, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Joseph Alexiou, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - [Land use law], 2009-2012 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - [Manufacturing land use], 2001 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Margaret Maugenest, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Pratt Institute, 1999-2012 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Tidal wetlands, 2004-2009 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Toxics targeting, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Urban Divers Estuary Conservancy, 2006-2009 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Series 5: Clippings and magazines
  - Agriculture [and urban farming], 2009-2012 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Bill de Blasio, 2005-2016 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Bridge magazine clippings, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - [Brooklyn history], 1986-2015 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Brooklyn Tomorrow magazine, 2007-2014 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Channel 13 used archival material, 2003-2009 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Climate, 2013-2015 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Culture and arts in Gowanus, 2003-2012 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Development, 2005-2015 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Environment issues, 1999-2014 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, 2010-2014 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Flooding, 2007-2013 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - FROGG press, 1999-2017 (Box 8, Folder 13-14)
  - Gentrification, 2006-2015 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Gowanus, 1973-1999 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Gowanus, 2000-2017 (Box 8, Folder 17-19)
  - Gowanus Canal, 2003-2006 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Gowanus development, 2005-2014 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Gowanus rezoning, 2008-2009 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Gowanus sludge, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - [Historic districts], 2012-2013 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Historic preservation, 2007-2013 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - History tours, 2009-2011 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Housing, 2004-2014 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Hurricane Sandy, 2012-2013 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Landmarks, 2002-2015 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Land use, 2008-2013 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Magazines with articles related to Gowanus, 2005-2014 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Native Americans, 2005-2012 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - [Nature and wildlife], 2002-2014 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Newtown Creek, 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Newtown, Lowe's, Carroll Gardens, Red Hook, Atlantic Yards, 2010-2014 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - New York Magazine, 2004-2006 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Other Brooklyn neighborhoods, 2005-2015 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - [Parks and green spaces], 2004-2013 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Preservation, 2005-2016 (Box 9, Folder 19-22)
  - Real estate, 2007-2014 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Superfund designation and cleanup, 2009-2012 (Box 9, Folder 24-26)
  - Toll Brothers, 2008-2009 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Waterfront, 2005-2011 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Water issues, 1987-2006 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Water, sewage, global warming, 2007-2008 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Whole Foods, 2008-2012 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Zoning, 2002-2009 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Series 6: Photographs and audiovisual media
  - 130 Third Street, cassette, 2004 (Box 1)
  - Brooklyn Matters, DVD, 2007 (Box 1)
  - Brooklyn Navy Yard Admiral's Row Development, DVD, 2009 (Box 1)
  - Characters of Gowanus, DVD, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Coming Clean: Reclaiming the Gowanus Canal, DVD, 2005 (Box 1)
  - Environmental Protection Agency Pro Gowanus Canal Superfund, DVD, 2013 (Box 1)
  - Fragile Waterways, DVD, 2010 (Box 1)
  - FROGG Department of Environmental Conservation, cassette, 2005 (Box 1)
  - Gowanus Roots, DVD, 2004 (Box 1)
  - Greetings from Brooklyn, DVD, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Lavender Lake: Brooklyn's Gowanus Canal, VHS, circa 1999 (Box 1)
  - Photographs by Mark D. Phillips, circa 2005-2015 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - [Photographs] for the Board of Standards and Appeals testimony, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Photographs from the Urban Divers Estuary Conservancy, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Photographs of Department of Environmental Protection water sampling, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Photographs of FROGG superfund party, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Photographs of Gowanus Canal by Arthur Mortensen, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - [Photographs of Gowanus by Linda Mariano], 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - [Photographs of Gowanus flooding], 2007 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - [Photographs of industry and construction on the Gowanus Canal], 2002-2010 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - [Photographs of] new construction Bond St., 2007 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - [Photographs of] people being evicted from building on Union St., circa 2005-2010 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - [Photographs of pollution and combined sewage outflows on the Gowanus Canal], 2003-2009 (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
  - [Photographs] of Red Hook, circa 2005-2010 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - [Photograph of the Gowanus Canal by David Schlegel], 2011 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - [Photographs of the] Whole Foods site, January, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - [Photographs of the] Whole Foods site at 3rd St., June, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - [Photographs of] unclean street ends, Sacket and Degraw, and other Gowanus wildflowers, etc., 2004 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - The Quavers filmed performing on the Gowanus Canal, DVD, 2007 (Box 1)
- Series 7: Printed materials and ephemera
  - Brownfields by Laura Nash, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Calendars, 2013-2014 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Central Brooklyn Independent Democrats, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - City Environmental Quality Review Technical Manual, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Digital graphics files, 2005-2014 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Eco-Gowanus: Urban Remediation by Design, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Event posters, 2007-2016 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - [Flyers and press releases from arts and cultural events], 2007-2017 (Box 10, Folder 13-14)
  - [Flyers related to environmental issues and advocacy], 2001-2014 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - [Flyers related to historic preservation and landmarking], 1998-2011 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Flyers related to Lightstone Group Development, 2012-2014 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - FROGG event flyers and press releases, 2007-2009 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Gowanus by Curtis Hamilton, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Gowanus Canal Walk, circa 2000-2007 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Historic preservation booklets, 1983-2010 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Liberum Kayak, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Maps, 1983-2013 (Box 10, Folder 21, Box 11, Folder 7, 13, Folder Flat File 2)
  - Newsletters, 2005-2014 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - New York City tourism pamphlets, circa 2007-2016 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - [Pins], 2009-2013 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - [Postcards], 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Protest posters and flyers, 2007-2015 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Real estate and development ephemera, 2004-2016 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - [Satellite image of Gowanus Canal corridor], circa 2002-2017 (Folder Flat File 3)
  - Signs, 2012-2016 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - The Best of Brooklyn: A Borough of Manufacturers, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Woodlands, Wetlands, and Wildlife, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 28)